judici.com 2010-11-23

# Judici Privacy Policy

**_Judici.com Privacy Policy_**

Judici.com and its subsidiaries ("Judici.com," "we," "us," or "our") know that you care about how your personal information is used and safeguarded. Judici.com wants to provide you with information concerning our collection, use and sharing of your personal information. This Privacy Policy addresses Judici.com's information handling practices related to personal information collected through www.judici.com. Please print a copy of this Privacy Policy for your records by using the print function of your browser. In addition, a link to the page containing this Privacy Policy is available on our homepage at http://www.judici.com. Please bookmark our homepage or write down and save the web address of our homepage so you can access our Privacy Policy (and any updates thereto) at a later date.

**PLEASE BE AWARE THAT, IN CONJUNCTION WITH YOUR USE OF WEBSITES, IN SOME INSTANCES JUDICI.COM IS PROVIDED WITH PERSONAL INFORMATION ABOUT YOU MAINTAINED BY CIVIL AND CRIMINAL COURTS ("COURT DATA"). IN ADDITION, FOR E-PAY USERS, WHEN YOU USE THE WEBSITE, JUDICI.COM PROVIDES YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION TO CIVIL AND CRIMINAL COURTS ("COURTS"). THESE CIVIL AND CRIMINAL COURTS SET THEIR OWN POLICIES CONCERNING THE HANDLING, PROTECTION, USE, DISCLOSURE AND PRIVACY OF COURT DATA AND PERSONAL INFORMATION PROVIDED TO THEM. JUDICI.COM IS NOT RESPONSIBLE FOR THE POLICIES OF COURTS WITH RESPECT TO SUCH COURT DATA OR PERSONAL INFORMATION PROVIDED TO THEM. IF YOU WOULD LIKE TO DETERMINE HOW A COURT HANDLES, PROTECTS, USES OR DISCLOSES COURT DATA OR YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION, OR THE PRIVACY PRACTICES OF A COURT, YOU MUST OBTAIN THEIR PRIVACY POLICY (IF APPLICABLE) OR CONTACT THE COURT DIRECTLY.**

This Privacy Policy is made up of the following sections:

  1. **Who Should Read This Privacy Policy**
  2. **The Information Judici.com Collects**
  3. **How We Use Personal Information**
  4. **How We Share or Disclose Personal Information**
  5. **Your Choices Concerning Judici.com's Handling of Your Personal Information**
  6. **How We Secure Your Information**
  7. **How You Can Access or Correct Your Information**
  8. **Links to Other Sites**
  9. **Changes to this Privacy Policy**
  10. **Privacy Contact -- How To Contact Us**

* * *

  1. **Who Should Read This Privacy Policy.** In general, this Privacy Policy addresses Judici.com's information handling practices related to the personal information of users that is collected and processed by Judici.com through [www.judici.com](http://www.judici.com/) and the applications and services accessible there (the "Website"). Therefore any person using the Website and/or any applications available at the Website should carefully review this Privacy Policy. However, Judici.com's practices concerning the collection, use and sharing of your personal information may vary depending on how you use the Website. The following types of users exist for the Website:
    1. **Subscribers** are users of any Subscription Service offered through the Website, as identified in <http://www.judici.com/service/permalinkJSA0808.jsp>
    2. **E-Pay Users** are users of the Judici E-Pay/E-Plea service offered through the Website for making court pleas and payments using the Website
    3. **Anonymous Users** are users of the Website who do not log in as a Subscriber or use the Judici E-Pay/E-Plea service.

Throughout this Privacy Policy Judici.com identifies instances where particular information handling practices apply to particular types of users. You should carefully review this Privacy Policy in order to understand not only Judici.com's general personal information handling practices, but also those that apply to you if you qualify as one or more of the user types set forth above.

  2. **The Information Judici.com Collects**

    1. If you are a Subscriber and/or E-Pay User, Judici.com will collect your contact data ("Contact Data") including for example, your name, phone number, home address and email address, and data necessary to execute a payment transaction ("Payment Data"), including for example, payment card number, billing address, card expiration date and payment amount.
    2. If you are an E-Pay User, Judici.com will also collect your plea (for example, guilty or not guilty), and data used to locate and process the case that you want to make a plea and/or payment for (collectively "E-Pay Case Data"), including for example the following information: driver's license number, date of birth, ticket number, zip code, and payment amount. In addition, in order to process your transaction using the Judici E-Pay/E-Plea service, we will receive Court Data from the Court about you and the case that you want to make a plea for.
    3. In addition, for all users of the Website, we collect the Internet protocol ("IP") address associated with the computer or Internet Service Provider you are using to visit the Website. As you browse the Website, we gather data that shows what pages you visited on the Website and how long you used various Website features and Services, collectively known as "Clickstream Data". We aggregate this information so that it is anonymous, cannot reveal your identity and is not linked to you personally ("Aggregate Non-personal Information").
    4. The Website uses "cookies." A cookie is a small piece of data stored locally by your browser that saves information and identifies your computer in some way. We use both a session ID cookie and a persistent cookie. A session ID cookie is a randomly-generated and unique identification number stored by your browser only during a given browser session. Session ID cookies ("Session ID Cookie") expire when you close your browser. A Session ID cookie is used by Judici.com to facilitate the proper functioning of the features of the Website. For example, it lets you easily return to your last search, lets Subscribers track the items in their shopping cart, and enables users to complete a multi-step process such as when E-Pay Users make an electronic plea or payment.
      1. A persistent cookie is a cookie that persists from session to session and is not deleted when you close your browser. We use a persistent cookie to store information about your use of the Website, including for example, to identify you as a returning user for purposes of developing Aggregate Non-personal Information. Persistent cookies are also used to track and target the preferences and interests of our returning users to enhance the experience on our Website.
      2. You may have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline all cookies if you prefer. Alternatively, you may be able to modify your browser setting to notify you each time a cookie is offered and permit you to accept or decline cookies on an individual basis. If you choose to decline cookies, however, that may hinder performance and you may not be able to use the Website.

  3. **How We Use Personal Information**

    1. We use Contact Data collected from you to communicate with you concerning your use of the Website, including communications concerning the services available through the Website, payments, billing and assistance with your use of the Website. We also use Contact Data and Payment Data to process payment card transactions related to any paid services you use through the Website and to bill you for such services.
    2. We use IP addresses to administer the Website and audit the use of the Website, including for purposes of enforcing compliance with Judici.com Terms of Use and to protect the Website from fraudulent behavior.
    3. We use Clickstream Data to provide you relevant advertising. We record portions of the Clickstream Data, specifically the searches made and Court Data viewed by Subscribers, in the event we need to investigate compliance with laws related to consumer credit reporting.
    4. We use Aggregate Non-personal Information to understand how users actually use the Website, and to improve the Website.
    5. If you are a Subscriber utilizing paid subscription services, we use the Contact Data and Payment Data you provide to establish a user identification and password and set up your Website account. When you visit the Website to use paid subscription services we will ask you to input your user identification and password so that we can verify that you are authorized to one or more paid subscription services.
    6. If you are an E-Pay User, we will use the E-Pay Case Data you provide to access and process your plea and/or payment for the case(s) you select.

  4. **How We Share or Disclose Information**

    1. Judici.com shares Payment Data and Contact Data with various service providers and intermediaries for the purpose of executing payment transactions, including for example payment card processors and banks.
    2. If you are an E-Pay User, we will share Payment Data, Contact Data and E-Pay Case Data you provide to us with the appropriate Court for purposes of recording and processing pleas and payments initiated by you through the Website. Note that some of the information E-Pay Users provide to us will be become part of the records of the Courts that receive it from us, including, for example, pleas made using the Website. When information becomes part of a Court's record it is subject to the Court privacy policies and practices. If you would like to determine how a court handles, protects, uses, makes available or discloses your personal information, or the privacy practices of a court, you must obtain their privacy policy (if applicable) or contact the court directly. Please note that while we collect your full payment card number to process payments related to the Judici E-Pay/E-Plea service of the Website, we only provide Courts with the last four digits of your card number.
    3. We also share Aggregated Non-personal Information with Courts and other third parties, including for example, advertisers, marketers, service providers, business partners and retailers, in order to operate the Website and add additional features, functionality and services.
    4. Judici.com will also disclose the personal information you provide to us under the following conditions:

      1. if required to do so by law, court order, as requested by other government or law enforcement authority, or in the good faith belief that disclosure is otherwise necessary or advisable;
      2. to protect the rights or properties of Judici.com, or when we have reason to believe that disclosing the information is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be interfering with our rights or property, whether intentionally or otherwise, or when anyone else could be harmed by such activities; and
      3. under circumstances where, whether for strategic or other business reasons, Judici.com decides to sell, buy, merge or otherwise reorganize its business, including in the event of bankruptcy. If such a transaction occurs, the purchasers, creditors, trustees or other persons or entities involved in such sale, purchase, merger or reorganization may have access to your personal information as a result of such sale, purchase, merger or reorganization.

  5. **Your Choices Concerning Judici.com's Handling of Your Personal Information.** If you do not wish for Judici.com, or the entities or persons described in this Privacy Policy to have access to or obtain your personal information, or disagree with Judici.com's collection or intended use of your personal information, then please do not use the Website or input your personal information into the Website, and be aware that you may not be able to use various services made available on the Website.

  6. **How We Secure Your Information.** Judici.com utilizes appropriate physical, technical and administrative controls and procedures to safeguard the information we collect from loss, misuse and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration and destruction. However, we cannot guarantee that those controls and procedures will never be defeated or fail, or that those controls or procedures will always be sufficient or effective. In our efforts to protect your online transactions, we use a technology called Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) to encrypt your personal information during the time it is sent over the Internet to or from the Website by Judici.com.

  7. **How You Can Access or Correct Your Information.**

    1. Contact Data provided by Subscribers can be accessed and corrected by Subscribers via the Account section of the Subscribers page of Judici.com.
    2. E-Pay Users and Subscribers can correct any Payment Data, and E-Pay Users can correct E-Pay Case Data, entered for a transaction, as long as they have not moved past the confirmation screen for that transaction. After confirmation of a transactions, Payment Data and E-Pay Case Data can no longer be corrected through Judici.com. Our policies with respect to accessing and correcting Payment Data after confirmation are stated in our refund policy, which is available at <http://www.judici.com/service/refund_policy.jsp>. In addition, if you wish to access or correct E-Pay Case Data after confirmation (including without limitation changing a plea entered into the Court Data as a disposition) you must contact the relevant Court that received the E-Pay Case Data.
    3. In addition, original Court Data is not main tained by Judici.com. If you conduct a search of your own Court Data and you determine that the Court Data about you is inaccurate or in need of correction, only the relevant Court which maintains that Court Data can make any necessary corrections. If you believe that such corrections are necessary, you should contact the Court directly or contact us as indicated on our Consumer Rights page, which is available via a link from the Judici.com home page.
    4. Please note, the most effective way to ensure the reliability, completeness and accuracy of your personal information in our records is to take care that you or your intermediary inputs your information correctly.

  8. **Links to Other Sites.** Links to other websites may be embedded in Judici.com's website or accessible from Judici.com's website. Please note that when you click on one of these links, you are entering another website for which Judici.com has no responsibility. We encourage you to read the privacy policies of all such sites as their policies may be materially different from this Privacy Policy.

  9. **Changes to this Privacy Policy.** We reserve the right to modify this Privacy Policy at any time, so please review it frequently. If we decide to change our Privacy Policy, we will post a notification of such change in the News Section of Judici.com and provide link to the updated Privacy Policy. Subscribers will find the News Section on the subscriber login page when they log in. All other users of the Website will find the News Section on the Case Search page they use. Any such modifications shall be effective as of the date indicated at the top of the Privacy Policy page. If you continue to use the Website after the changed Privacy Policy has been posted, we will consider that to be your acceptance of and consent to the changes in the revised Privacy Policy. This includes your consent for any personal information that we may collect and use starting on the effective date of the revised Privacy Policy as well as for any personal information that we have obtained prior to the effective date of the revised Privacy Policy.

  10. **Privacy Contact -- How to Contact Us.** Should have any questions or need to contact us about this Privacy Policy, please sent us an email at:

privacy@judici.com

Or send us a letter to:

Judici.com  
PO Box 803338 #66574  
Chicago, Illinois 60680-3338   
Fax: 618-549-0675  
ATTN: Privacy 

* * *

ID DN10 v.6 03/05/09 

**Revision History:**  
v.6 (Baseline release) - Effective 06/04/2009
